Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee College of Letters & Science Records, 1948-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
UW-Milwaukee College of Letters & Science Records, 1948-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. College of Letters & Science. Office of the Dean
UWM Archival Collection 1
Accession 2002-071
Accession 2009-063
Accession 2010-068(2)
Accession 2013-011
Accession 2016-003
Accession 2016-032
73.9 cubic ft. (83 boxes) plus additions of 23 cubic ft. (36 boxes)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Records of the largest academic division at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee (UWM), which administers numerous centers, departments, and programs. The records document the administration of the college's seven deans: Joseph G. Baier (1956-1966), Roy G. Francis (1966-1969), Howard J. Pincus (1969-1972), William F. Halloran (1972-1998), Marshall Goodman (1999-2002), Richard Meadows (2002-2011), and Rodney Swain (2011-2017). Most of the records date from 1965 to 2000, but the collection contains a few records of UWM's predecessor institutions. The majority of the records are correspondence and reports between the deans, associate deans, and the department heads concerning academic activities, curriculum development, and program funding. The files also contain records of numerous ad hoc and standing college committees, and committees organized within the departments. Also included are photos of faculty, student life, departmental functions, and other events sponsored by the College.
The University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee was created in 1956 following the merger of the University of Wisconsin's Milwaukee Center and the Wisconsin State College, Milwaukee. The College of Letters & Science was established at the time of merger. Joseph G. Baier was named dean, and he served until 1966.
Histories of the college can be found in The First Ten Years and Forum 1977. Both are available in the collection and in the UWM Libraries.
Deans of the College
1956-1966 Joseph G. Baier
1966-1969 Roy G. Francis
1969-1972 Howard J. Pincus
1972-1998 William F. Halloran
1999-2002 Marshall Goodman
2002-2011 G. Richard Meadows
2011-2016 Rodney Swain
2017- Dave Clark (interim)
Records of the largest academic division at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee (UWM), which administers numerous centers, departments, and programs. The records document the administration of the college's six deans: Joseph G. Baier (1956-1966), Roy G. Francis (1966-1969), Howard J. Pincus (1969-1972), William F. Halloran (1972-1998), Marshall Goodman (1999-2002), and Richard Meadows (2002-2011). Most of the records date from 1965 to 1980, but the collection contains a few records from UWM's predecessor institutions and three boxes of post-1980 material from the Halloran administration.
The majority of the collection consists of the dean's files concerning the centers, departments, and programs within the college. The records document the development of new courses and degrees; staffing and equipment needs; plans for future expansion; and efforts to streamline operations. Also included are copies of correspondence, reports, and background materials either created by the dean or sent to him from other offices. The files also contain agendas, minutes, and supporting materials from departmental ad hoc and standing committees.
The files often contain frank assessments written by the faculty or staff most intimately involved with the operations, which are very useful in understanding the development of plans and programs. In many cases, correspondence between the vice chancellor and the dean found in the departmental files also provides useful documentation. Among the most well-documented operations are the Centers for Latin American and Twentieth Century Studies; the Departments of Chemistry, English, and Mass Communication; the Honors Program; Master of Arts in Foreign Language and Literature Program; and the WUWM radio station.
The records of the Academic Deans Council document the L&S Dean's involvement in general administrative concerns such as the budget, relevant decisions of the UW System Regents, and grading and salary policies.
There are numerous records concerning the relations with the local African-American community and minority students at UWM. Materials can be found in files on "Achievements, Plans, Resources"; the Ad Hoc Committee on Afro-American Students; affirmative action plan; Black student advising; the proposed 1968 mentor project; minority students; and the Dept. of Afro-American Studies. Controversies concerning the cancellation of radio programs aimed at the African American community are well documented in the files pertaining to the WUWM radio station.
The chancellor's files, which are most extensive for the early 1960s, usually contain correspondence regarding general policy issues. Of interest are occasional letters from Chancellor Klotsche regarding the division of responsibility for a program between the College and another academic unit.
The correspondence files contain the dean's incoming and outgoing letters with individuals on and off the campus, usually concerning general policy issues, funding, staffing, and other administrative concerns. The files also contain some copies of the correspondence of other university personnel when it pertained to college operations. There is overlap in the files of correspondence for the years 1964-1966. Some of the correspondence can also be found in the files on committees, centers, departments, and programs.
The records of the Course and Curriculum Committee normally contain agendas, minutes, and supporting materials. The committee reviewed plans for new degrees, majors, and minors. It also discussed and approved course action requests such as changing a course description or title, or adding and dropping courses. The committee, appointed by the dean, met about every two weeks.
The records of the Dean's Faculty Advisory Committee normally contain agendas, minutes, and supporting materials. The committee met monthly to discuss general issues with the dean that were raised by the Committee members. The records of the college's faculty meetings normally contain the agendas, minutes, and supporting materials. The faculty approved recommendations for consideration of candidates for degrees and honors, and approved annual reports and special reports of the committees within the College. The faculty met once in the spring semester and once in the fall semester.
Files on the history of the college include a copy of The First Ten Years, written by Dean Joseph Baier in 1975, and the proceedings, and audio and video recordings of Forum 1977, a symposium celebrating the 20th anniversary of the college.
The collection contains an extensive run of the memos sent by the dean and the assistant and associate deans to members of the college. Most of the memos concern routine procedural matters about meetings, or budgetary, staff, or student affairs.
An excellent overview of the college's operations and plans in the 1970s is the files containing "Ten Year Plans," and for the 1980s in the files containing "Achievements, Plans, Resources." The latter normally include a formal organizational chart, and detailed analyses of affirmative action plans, budgets, student retention, workloads, and other issues.
The statistical analyses and reports contain both summary and detailed information on class size and cumulative grade point averages; and the number of courses, sections, and students. The information is presented in graphs and tables.
The collection contains extensive correspondence between the dean and the vice chancellor, copies of which can sometimes be found in the departmental files. The correspondence usually discusses funding and staff levels for college operations or major changes in university procedures.
Also included in the collection is a selection of photographs from various Letters & Science events and publications. The majority of these are portrait photos of faculty and staff, but also present are photos of students and alumni, including documentation of the 1999-2000 Alumni College. There are numerous photos of student life, such as students in class and laboratories, students clubs & groups, and the freshmen scholar picnic. A folder of departmental files includes scenes from events sponsored by the departments of Forensic Science, Psychology, and Biology, among others.
This collection was received in, and is organized in, multiple parts. Additional materials have not been physically or intellectually arranged and interfiled, and researchers may need to consult more than one part of the collection to locate similar materials.
UWM Archival Collection 1: Records, 1948-2014
The collection is arranged into the following series:
Subject Files, 1948-2014
Publicity Files, 1970-2009
The files are organized alphabetically by folder heading within each series.
The collection contains five additional accessions.
Accession 2002-071: Personnel Files, 1965-1998
Accession 2009-063: Personnel Files, 1956-2009
Accession 2010-068(2): Personnel Files, 1997
Accession 2013-011: Personnel Files, 1964-2013
Accession 2016-003: Personnel Files, 1960-2011
Accession 2016-032: Subject and Personnel Files, 1968-2013
Finding aids for the personnel files in boxes 36-56, and for accessions 2002-071, 2009-063, 2010-068(2), 2013-011, and 2016-003 are available in the Archives.
An item-level inventory of the photographs in series 2 is available as a spreadsheet in the Archives. The spreadsheet includes the subject and date of the photographs (if known), as well as correspondence to photo jobs from the UWM Photo Services Collection (UWM AC 214).
Administrative/Restriction Information
The unclassified personnel files in boxes 36-56 and in accessions 2002-071, 2009-063, 2010-068, 2013-011, 2016-003, and 2016-032 (boxes 11-15) are restricted in accordance with UWM Personnel File Policy S-42. Access is regulated by Section III. A.2 and III. A.3. There are no access restrictions on the rest of the collection, which is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
The collection originally consisted of 33 processed and unprocessed accessions acquired before 1989. In October 1997 Anne Potter transferred an accession (1995-022) of personnel files. William Halloran transferred some project materials (1998-049) in 1999. An additional accession (2006-013) was transferred in 2006. The College of Letters & Science transferred accession 2011-029 in November 2011. The College transferred additional materials in June 2010 (accession 2009-063), August 2013 (accession 2013-011), July 2016 (2016-003), and February 2017 (accession 2019-032). Dept. of Philosophy personnel files were transferred to the Archives in January 2003 (accession 2002-071) and Dept. of Psychology personnel files were transferred in June 2011 (accession 2010-068).
Contents List
- Records, 1948-2014, UWM Archival Collection 1; 73.9 cubic ft. (83 boxes)
  - 1. Subject Files, 1948-2014
    - 30th Anniversary of Merger, Faculty Party, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Academic Affairs Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Academic Computing, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Academic Deans Council
      - 1969-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3-19)
      - Retreat, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Academic Planning Committee, 1981-1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Academic Policy Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Academic Program, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 24-25)
    - Academic Staff Policy and Procedures, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Accreditation of L & S Programs, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Achievements, Plans, Resources
      - 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - 1983-1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Afro-American Studies
      - 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
      - Black Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Black Student Analyses, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
      - Questionnaire on Black Faculty, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Reviewers, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Subcommittee on Student Support Services, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Bachelor of Liberal Arts, 1967-1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty Sabbatical Program, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Future Use of Space in the North Wing of Lapham Hall, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Honors, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Honors Designations, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Language Learning, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 18-20)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Medieval Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Problems Facing Freshmen, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Student Absences, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Student Loans, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the College Level Examination Program, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Undergraduate Degree Requirements, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 26-29)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Urban Planning, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Women's Recruitment, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Ad Hoc Committee to Study Proposal for Social Science Research Project, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Ad Hoc Teaching Evaluation Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Ad Hoc Transfer Policy Committee, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Administrative Affairs, 1970-1984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Admissions and Records, 1957-1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Admissions Policy Committee, 1975-1984 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Advising Office, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Advisory Committee for the Language Resource Center, 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Affirmative Action Plan, 1993-1994 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action Program, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Afro-American Conference on Black Scholarship, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Afro-Urban Institute, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Allied Health Education Advisory Council of South-Eastern Wisconsin, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Alumni Association, 1966-1976 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Alumni Relations, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - American Civilization Course, 1956-1963 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
    - American Federation of Teachers, 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - American Geographical Society Collection, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - American Men of Science, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Applied Mathematics and Physics Major, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Applied Science and Engineering, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Approval Matrix Revision, 2006
      Records captured as part of UWM Web Collection.
    - Associate Degree, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Atmospheric Sciences, 1972-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9-14)
    - Auditing Courses, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Bacteriology Major, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Baldwin, I. L., Meetings with Departments, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Benkley Property, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Biennial Budget, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 19-21)
    - Biological Aspects of Conservation Major, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Black Student Advising, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Brochures, 1975-1987, 1994-1996, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Budget, 1956-1962 (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
    - Budget Control, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Budget Planning Document: 1993-1994, 1994-1995, and 1996-1997, 1993, 1995 (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
    - Budget Planning Document: 1995-1996, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Buildings and Grounds, 1959-1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Business and Liberal Arts Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Business-Economics Building, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Business Office, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Cable TV, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
    - Cable TV Course, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Calendar Committee, 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Capital Equipment, 1976-1985 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Carl Shurz Professorship Committee, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Cedarburg Bog Study, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 38-39)
    - Center for American Indian and Spanish Speaking Affairs, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Center for Great Lakes Studies, 1971-1978 (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
    - Center for Latin American Studies
      - 1968-1985 (Box 4, Folder 4-9)
      - Advisory Committee, 1972-1985 (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
      - Certificate, 1976-1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Grant Projects, 1967-1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Grant Proposals, 1972-1985 (Box 4, Folder 14-17)
      - Research Funded, 1972-1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Secretariat, 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Center for Twentieth Century Studies
      - 1968-1978 (Box 4, Folder 20-33)
      - 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
      - 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - "Technology and the Social Imagination," NEH Grant, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
      - "Trojan Horse" Project, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - CETA, 1977-1980 (Box 5, Folder 8-13)
    - Chairmen's Meetings
      - 1956-1974 (Box 5, Folder 14-19)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
      - 1984 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Chancellor, 1956-1985 (Box 5, Folder 23-33)
    - Chemistry Building, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Civilization Course, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, Miscellaneous, 1972-1973, 1979-1980 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Clodius, Robert L., 1962-1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Codification Committee, 1966-1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - College Degree Requirements Committee, 1971-1981 (Box 6, Folder 5-6)
    - College Level Examination Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - College Level Examination Program, 1972-1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - College of Engineering and Applied Science, 1964-1983 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
    - College of Letters and Science Guidebooks, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - College of Letters and Science Instruction and Budget Reports, 1998-2013
    - College of Letters and Science (Madison), 1956-1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - College of Letters and Science, School of Education Liaison Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Collegium, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Columbia Hospital Project, 1974-1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Commencement, 1957-1966 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Commerce Division, 1959-1964 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Committee for Undergraduate Research, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Committee Interdisciplinary Major, 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Biochemistry and Molecular Biology, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Elementary Language Instruction, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Committee on Innovations in Teaching and Grading, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1971-1978 (Box 6, Folder 23-30)
    - Committee on Integrated Liberal Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Committee on Linguistics, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Committee on Merit Increases, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Committee on Teaching Assistants, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Committee on the Comparative Study of Religion, 1977-1981 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Community Advisory Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 34-35)
    - Community Relations Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Community Seminar Advisory Committee, 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Comparative Study of Religion, Academic Planning Document, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Computer Aided Instruction, 1975-1985 (Box 6, Folder 38-39)
    - Computer Classrooms, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Computer Committee, 1959-1966 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Computer Funding, 1973-1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Computer Policy Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Computer Science MS, 1973-75 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
    - Conference Committee, 1956-1962 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Conference on Linguistic Categorization, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Contemporary Trends Program, 1963-1976 (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
    - Cooperative Educational Program
      - 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 10-11)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Coordinating Council for Higher Education, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
    - Correspondence
      - 1956-1967 (Box 7, Folder 15-32)
      - 1968-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1-9)
      - 1972-1993 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Department Chairs, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 10-11)
    - Council on Academic Advising, 1967-1971 (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
    - Course and Curriculum Committee
      - 1956-1977 (Box 8, Folder 14-32)
      - 1978-1990 (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
    - Cultural and Technological Studies Program, 1971-1985 (Box 9, Folder 5-14)
    - Cultures and Communities, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1964-1970 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Curriculum Study
      - Departments A-I, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Departments J-S, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Executive Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Minutes, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Curtin Hall
      - 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Special Equipment, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Dean's Day, 1961-1965 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Dean's Faculty Advisory Committee
      - 1966-1973 (Box 9, Folder 24-27)
      - 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Debate Program, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Degree Designations, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Degree Opportunity Study, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Departments of Communication and Mass Communication, Program Reviews, 1973-1984 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Dept. of Afro-American Studies, 1973-1986 (Box 10, Folder 6-12)
    - Dept. of Anthropology
      - 1973-1986 (Box 10, Folder 13-17)
      - MS/PhD Program Reviews, 1968-1979 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Planning Documents, 1983-1985 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Art History
      - 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - 1977-1986 (Box 10, Folder 19-25)
      - MA Program, 1975-1977 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Planning Documents, 1982-1985 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Biological Sciences
      - 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1948-1986 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1984-1987 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Five Year Program Review, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Graduate Program Review Report, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - PhD, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - PhD Steering Committee, 1977-1984 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Planning Document, 1986-1991 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Program Brochures, undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Dept. of Botany
      - 1973-1984 (Box 10, Folder 27-30)
      - Five Year Graduate Program Review, 1973, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Graduate Program, 1971-1976 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Planning Document, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Chemistry
      - 1973-1986 (Box 11, Folder 1-17)
      - Audit and Review, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - MS and PhD Program Reviews, 1968-1978 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Planning Document, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Graduate Research in Chemistry and Biochemistry,1990 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Dept. of Classics
      - 1973-1985 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Dept. of Classics, Planning Documents, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Dept. of Communication
      - 1963-1970 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - 1973-1986 (Box 11, Folder 22-29)
      - Planning Documents, 1982-1985 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Comparative Literature
      - 1973-1986 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
      - Academic Planning Document: 1983-1984, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Dept. of Economics
      - 1973-1986 (Box 12, Folder 4-13)
      - Cost of PhD, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 14)